Hi!
I'm going to show you some easy to do magic ticks that you can perform at work.
Once you've done the rubber band finger cuff trick and everybody's recovering from the shock and awe of the illusion, drop one of the elastics when they're not looking.
Then take 2 fingers, put them through the remaining elastic and twist.
Then take your thumb, go underneath the whole thing up and around into that little bundle from the left hand.
Pull out your middle finger, then go back into this position.
Now it looks exactly there's 2 elastics; just like the previous trick.
Make a big deal about it.
Then say well this time we're going to change it up a bit.
This time I'm just going to make this one disappear.
Put your finger and thumb together, let the elastic roll off into a little knot.
A little bit of magic and it's gone.